Hello Hello
Здравствуйте Здравствуйте
from the city of Khmelnitsky Where are you from
из города Хмельницкий Вы откуда
I'm from Moscow
Я из Москвы
interesting
интересненько
unexpectedly
неожиданно
bees I don't know there were different cities there
пчел Я не знаю тут разные города там
were all sorts of Murmansk some
всякие были Мурманск какой-то
Novosibirsk Birobidzhan interesting
Новосибирск Биробиджан интересно
interesting fact these people who
интересный факт вот эти люди которые
were not from Moscow they were in the Kremlin
были не из Москвы они были в Кремле
much more times than me
гораздо больше раз чем я
cool
прикольно
And  I can also say that I’m from a village
И я также могу сказать что я из деревни
located near Zhytomyr
которая находится под Житомир
Why did I just tell you just said
Почему просто рассказал просто рассказал
well done
молодец
you have ships on your wall There’s a nautical map
у тебя на стене корабли Там карта
in one room I made the other no
в одной комнате сделал другой нет
laziness and beer it’s
лень и пиво
cool
прикольно
how does it relate to the fact that Russia attacked
как относится к тому что Россия напала
Ukraine
на Украину
when I
когда
didn’t hear anything yesterday  about this, it’s
не слышал ничего об этом
cool, probably drunk, overslept,
прикольно наверно бухал проспал
no, I worked yesterday, I’m
нет вчера работал
clearly not a knowledge worker,
вот явно не работник умственного труда
but
правда
I’m a programmer by training in
я программист по образованию
microcontrollers, and I work as a
микроконтроллеров и работаешь
programmer, and I work as a programmer, for
программистом и работаю программистом
the first time, all the
нифигасе впервые все таблетки
programmers’ tablets, I met some
программистов встретил какие-то
builders. You won’t believe it, for the first time in chat
строители Вот не поверишь впервые в чат
roulette and you went in and
рулетку и зашел
you’re programming them
ты их программируешь
now  I work as an integrator using a
сейчас работаю интеграторе на
script, I program
скрипте программирую
in this situation, I started.
в данной ситуации начала
Before that I worked in Python, I initially
До этого работал на питоне изначально
studied and said that JavaScript and Java
учился и сказал там JavaScript и Java
are the same thing or are they different, are they
это одно и то же или это разные это
different, why am I confused? I don’t know
разные то зачем запутался Я не знаю
JavaScript, it’s more about web design
JavaScript это больше веб-дизайну идет
now that I’m working on the load system
сейчас по работе нагрузочную систему
I write for all sorts of platforms
пишу для всяких платформ
load load testing
нагрузочная нагрузочное тестирование
you load the system Yes, when I write
ты нагружаешься систему Да когда пишу
saying software that loads a
говоря софт который нагружает
certain site What task is there to
определенный сайт Какая задача стоит там
test basic things how many
протестить элементарные вещи сколько
users can log in I remember In
пользователей может заходить Я помню
short, at school we had computer science and
Короче у нас в школе была информатика и
there this too, or Java or
там вот это тоже или Java или
javascrible and there  in short, the teacher gave something like this:
javascrible и там короче преподном давал
there is and plus And there is plus
такое что-то вот есть и плюс А есть плюс
plus how it differed in the exam at
плюс чем она отличалась на экзамене в
school
школе
Well, look when after and pluses is written and
Ну смотри когда после и плюсы пишется и
even now modern traces of development
уже сейчас современных следах разработки
are not written And plus plus is written roughly
не пишется А плюс плюс пишется грубо
speaking, there are cycles and in a cycle if you
говоря есть циклы и в цикле если ты
you write plus plus costs So each
пишешь плюс плюс стоит Значит каждый
cycle each action will add
цикл каждое действие будет прибавляться
plus 1 when you write oh pluses then
плюс 1 когда ты до пишешь ой плюсы то
this means -1
это значит -1
and roughly speaking it is cyclical That is, I will
и грубо говоря это циклируется То есть я
write plus plus it will be Minus one
напишу плюс плюс это будет Минус один
yes Yeah I understand that is, if two plus
да Ага понял то есть если два плюс
I leave after the letter  then it
оставлю после буквы то это она на плюс
will increase by plus one, and if there is 2 + in front of the letter,
один увеличится а если перед буквой 2 +
then it will decrease by one. Look, this is
а то на один уменьшится Смотри это
used as a rule from their forms
используется как правило с их форм
and it is written there, let’s say a value from
и там прописывается допустим значение от
one, let’s say, to whatever
единицы допустим до там какого
indicator you need, let’s say
показателя который тебе нужен допустим
up to 1000 and just these  pluses
до 1000 и как раз таки вот эти плюсы
will mean that let's say we have an
будут обозначать то что допустим у нас
equation, then we have to
есть уравнение то что мы должны каждый
add 30 each time and let's say 1 plus 30 31
раз прибавлять 30 и допустим 1 плюс 30
plus 30 61 plus 30
31 плюс 30 61 плюс 30
if I want a cycle, I can make
если я хочу цикл получается сделать
it increase, I write and plus plus
чтобы он увеличивался я пишу и плюс плюс
And so that plus decreases, so here it is  they
А чтобы уменьшался плюс так вот она на
cost one less yes
единицу меньше стоят да
Well, well, there was also such [ __ ] and
А хорошо а там еще была такая фигня и
minus Minus and minus Minus And what did that
минус Минус и минус Минус А что это
mean then
означало тогда
No idea, I
Без понятия
never wrote something like that Yes,
никогда не писал такое
these are the things
Да вот такие дела
I just can’t I’m waiting for [ __ ]
Я просто я не могу Я жду [__]
just a unique
просто уникальный
job they took it
работу взяли
with him
именно с ним
I  In short, I tried to hold on.
Я короче я старался держаться
Holy [ __ ], how would you write a cycle from 10
[__] то как бы ты написал цикл от 10
to one, a
до единицы
cycle for
цикл for
What language in Java
На каком языке на Джаве
for from 0 to 10 to 10 to 0
for от 0 до 10 до 10 до 0
no, from 0 to 10 not me, so that the cycle
нет от 0 до 10 не я вот чтобы цикл
Odessa A and equals 0 then a and equals  10
Одессе А и равно 0 дальше а и равно 10
don’t look like that, but on the contrary from 10 I typed
не так смотри а наоборот от 10 напечатал
10 9 here’s how to count backwards from 10 to 0 I’m
10 9 вот как обратный отчет от 10 до 0
then trying an
я тогда
Olympiad problem of a
олимпиадная задача
drunk person
пытаешься пьяного человека
I would use a library or
Я использовал бы библиотеку либо
write it in the standard way
прописал по стандартном пути
like this Well, let’s say, for example, there’s a
так Ну давай например
library that writes a loop
это библиотека есть которая цикл пишет
backwards,
задом наперед
of course, some kind of-  then the library in Java I would
конечно какая-то библиотека в Джаве бы я
do I don’t know
делаю не знаю
Maybe there is some kind of function there maybe there is some kind of
Может там какая-то может там какая-то
function there is a reverse for there is in short like I
функция там реверс for есть короче типа
don’t know the library is written for a
что не знаю библиотека написано чтобы
loop You can write given before
цикл Можно писать задано перед
Well look It’s elementary if you do it then
Ну смотри Элементарно если сделать то
just divide the answer let’s say with
просто делить ответ допустим с
[music  ]
[музыка]
divide by 10 without a remainder
делить на 10 без остатка
now
сейчас
Well, make the handicap which I
Ну сделать форы которые
also ran from
прогонял также от
one to 10 stood from 10 to 100 and
единицы до 10 стоял от 10 до 100 и
then make an equation made a
дальше сделать уравнение сделал
variable Before this, the Handicap which was
переменную До этого Фора которая была
equal to 100 and then just run,
равнялась 100 и дальше просто прогонять
let’s say 100 minus
допустим 100 минус
name the name of the variable, let’s say it
назвать имя переменной допустим это
will be a and  is equal to A minus 1 and each cycle is
будет а и равно А минус 1 и каждый цикл
-1 and here you go It’s
-1 и вот пожалуйста
amazing
[__]
if you ask to write a cycle
получается если цикл зададут написать
like from the largest to the smallest, this is already a
типа от большего к меньшему это уже
difficult task, yes,
сложная задача получается да
no, why
Да нет почему
just write a cycle of 10 steps and do
просто пишем цикл 10 шагов и делаем
the equation
уравнение
Well, let’s make a variable From what
Ну сделать переменную допустим С какого
number did we
числа мы
make X  is equal to 10 Yes, now the cycle is from
сделали X равно 10 Да теперь цикл от
one to ten And in this cycle of noise with
одного до десяти А в этом цикле шума с
this mix we do What equation do we make the
этим миксом делаем Какое уравнение мы
condition Let's say we enter
делаем условие Допустим мы вносим
ten into the variable
десятку в переменную
let's say And let this be further we
допустим А это пускай будет дальше мы
sit down with us a kilogram straight at a time autumn and the
сесть нами килограмм прям за раз осень а
experience
опыт
should
должен
YouTube driving us through  careers in the
YouTube загоняя нас через карьерки в
shadow ban and even then the video is not
теневый бан и дуже была то видео не
shown to people,
показывается людям часто показывается
information about streams is often shown for that
информация про стримы для того
quick curl
оперативный завиток
and pop there is
а попок там
video
видео
information and you and me
информация и мы с вами
[music]
[музыка]